If you want to open your Fund Bazaar account,
you can do it very easily by watching this video. In this video,
I have explained everything in detail with a live demo.
Through the Fund Bazaar account, you can invest in mutual funds through
SIP, lump sum, loan against
mutual funds, bank FD, NPS, gold
stocks etc. It is a very
good app, a very trusted app.
This Prudent company has been running since 2000 and is
providing excellent service till date. Let me
tell you a little bit that if you
open an account through this, then if your KYC
is already in place, then this video is for you. You will have to do your
KYC first.
If you
want to do your KYC yourself and understand the process, then
you can contact us.
I will tell you the entire process.
If you have KYC, then through this video
you can complete the further process
within 5 minutes. To open an account,
you should have Aadhar card, PAN
card, bank passbook or cancelled cheque
along with mobile number and email ID.  It
should also be there along with this your Aadhar number should be
linked to your bank account, if there are so many things
then you can open a Fund Bazaar account very easily,
okay, let's
watch the video, if you have any query anywhere, if you
need any help, then you
must contact us, we will get
your account opened absolutely free of cost,
okay and here if you
need our free advisory from time to time, if you want the
best funds, you should keep getting to know
which are the best funds from time to time, and here
our partner code is ER A 290 521,
definitely enter it, okay and after opening the account, if
you contact us, then we will
tell you the best funds and will make your
investment there and
you will keep getting absolutely free advisory free support till live time,
after clicking on the Fund Bazaar registration link, the option of Open Your Fund Bazaar will
come, here you have to enter your name, your
mobile number and your email ID, keep in
mind that your name should
match with the PAN card and Aadhar card,
after filling all the details, we will proceed,
here we will select Individual,
after this the email ID which you had entered  An
OTP will be sent on it, you have to enter the OTP here to
verify the email ID, after this there is a
mobile number option,
OTP will be sent on the mobile number, you will verify it by entering the mobile number,
after this
create any password of your choice here
and enter the same password again in the confirm password and
proceed further, now you will
enter the PAN number here and the
date of birth written in the PAN and
proceed further, if you have KYC then
all your details will be fetched from before,
okay now there are some details here
like your name, so according to the PAN
you have to enter your name here, annual
income has to be selected here,
you have to select the profession here, after this
in partner name Brijendra Kumar ARN
290 521 has to be selected, if it is not coming then
you can type here, after this
next button is given,
click on the next button, now here some things have to be
selected first residential status,
income source has to be selected, okay
after this here  The place of birth
means where you were born, you have to select it,
after this see, your Lite account will be
created, now here you have to
select your nominee, the name of the nominee,
date of birth
and what is the relationship of the nominee with you, is it
okay and you will select the relationship and
how much percentage do you want to give, then enter 100% here,
after this you will proceed and next,
OTP will be sent, you have to enter OTP from mobile
number or email ID, you have to verify it,
after this here comes the turn of
bank details, first of all you have to
enter IFC code here, as after entering IFC code you will
proceed, the bank will automatically appear,
see it has appeared, after this you will enter the account number
twice, after this you will proceed,
an OTP will come through CAMS, you will enter the OTP here,
okay, after this you will click next,
whatever your account is, see it will come in this way, it will be
automatically fetched,
again OTP will be sent for confirmation,
now this will
automatically take some processing and
after this see, all the details of your account will appear
here by default
here  But if the MICR code is not available then
enter it from the passbook here. If it is asking you to upload the passbook then you will
upload the passbook here. Many times you do
n't have to type your name here. Whatever is
your name in the bank, you will click next. Then the
OTP will be sent and your account will be
created here. So this will be the complete process of
creating an account. Now to
check the status of the Fund Bazaar account,
go to My Account, then go to Manage Client
and see here, it will be shown as Under Process.
It gets activated within 5 minutes. By
now you must have
opened your Fund Bazaar account. If you are
facing any problem anywhere, then
you can contact us without hesitation. Once
we contact you, you will be able to tell you
which are the best funds and in which you should invest.
You will get this entire service absolutely free for life.
We do not charge anything, it is absolutely
free, but this service
is only for those people who have entered our partner
code 290 5008. So,
I hope you liked the video.
Future updates for similar videos.  Please do
subscribe to the channel, thank you.